RAJ KAPOOR DEEPAK

DESKTOP SUPPORT ENGINEER | Mob. No. - 7250651758

Emil ID:- rajkapoordpk@gmail.com

Objective

Auenthusiastic IT professional with extensive experience in engineering, administrator and technical support of IT. I would like to obtain a position where my experience, education background and team-player attitude can best benefit your company with strong technical knowledge, implementation analysis and troubleshooting. To obtain a challenging position in a dynamic organization and be an integral part of growth oriented company. To utilize and grow my analytical, research and technical skills in Systems Administration.

Experience Summary

- Over 3 years of industrial experience in Microsoft Windows Platform.
- Good technical skills & troubleshooting skills.
- Excellent communication and customer management skills.

Job History Designation	Company	<u>Period</u>
Desktop Support Engineer	Hitachi Systems Micro Clinin Pvt Ltd	April 2017 to Present
Desktop Support Engineer	CMS Infosolution Pvt Ltd	April 2015 to March 2017
Customer Support Engineer	Renovision Automation Services Pvt Ltd	April 2014 to march 2015
Customer Support Engineer	Progressive Infosolution Pvt Ltd	Sep 2013 to March 2014

Computer Skills:

Server: Windows® (2000, 2003 & 2008 Server)

Client: Windows® (2000 Professional, XP, Vista, Windows7, Windows 8): MS Office (2000, 2003, 2007, 2010) (Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook), Open Office, Symantec Anti-Virus Server & Client, CA Service Desk, Team Viewer, Microsoft Office Outlook, Mozilla Firefox, Win Zip, Win Rar, Internet, Antivirus, Firewall, etc..

Technical Knowledge:

- > Assembling of PC's
- > Installation & Troubleshooting of Software's & Hardware Devices
- > Installation & Troubleshooting of Operating System
- > Installation and configuration of Symantec AV client ver. 12
- > Installation and troubleshooting of USB printer, multi-functional printer.
- Basic understanding and troubleshooting of LAN issues.
- Hands on experience on centralize Service Desk tool for day to day call logging.
- Installation & Configuration of Wireless Access Point, Bluetooth.
- Installation and troubleshooting of Email clients like MS Outlook.

Work Experience:

Total Experience: - >3 Years

Work Experience Details:

Working as a **Desktop Support Engineer** with CMS Infosolution Pvt Ltd, Mumbai & posted at its Client **Punjab National Bank, Circle Office-GAYA** from Sept 2014 onwards.

Work & Responsibility

- Supporting Of Computer Hardware, Software & Networking.
- > Troubleshooting Software through remotely.
- Escalation of customer issues with different levels of support.
- Configuration of Printers, Scanners through remotely.
- > Installation & Troubleshooting of Operating System (windows XP, Vista, 7, Windows 8 & 8.1)
- > Installation & Troubleshooting of Software's & Hardware Devices (Laptop/Desktop/Data Card).
- Maintains hardware, software & MS Office inventory.
- > Installation and troubleshooting of Email clients like MS Outlook, Outlook Express.
- > Supporting/Remote Location: 1) Arwal, 2) Gaya, 3) Jehanabad, 4) Aurangabad.

Academic

Education	Board/University	Year	% marks	Division
MCA	MAGADH UNIVERSITY, BODHGAYA	2017	<i>70.16%</i>	1st
BCA	MAGADH UNIVERSITY, BODHGAYA	2013	67.8%	1st
INTER	B.S.E.B. PATNA	2009	<i>63.4</i> %	1st
MATRIC	C.B.S.E. DELHI	2007	82.8%	1st

Technical Qualification

- (1) Diploma in Computer Applications
- (2) Typing Certificate

Languages Known

Hindi (Expert) & English (Medium)

Personal Details

Name: Raj Kapoor Deepak

Sex: Male

Date of Birth: 19th - March - 1992 (19/03/1992)

Father's Name: Bachan Kumar Sinha

Marital Status: Single Nationality: Indian Religion: Hindu

Permanent Address:

HOUSE NO-487, CHITRAGUPTA NAGAR, NEAR-AKSHAYWAT, MARANPUR, P.O.-CHAND CHAURA, P.S.-VISHNUPAD, GAYA-823001, BIHAR

Correspondence Address:

HOUSE NO-487, CHITRAGUPTA NAGAR, NEAR-AKSHAYWAT, MARANPUR, P.O.-CHAND CHAURA, P.S.-VISHNUPAD, GAYA-823001, BIHAR

Declaration:

On behalf of my Resume whatever I have written is true and legal Even if you find any false and wrong information I am ready to accept your decision. However, if you offer me an opportunity I will try my best to satisfy you by my hard, honest and skillful work.

Place:- Gaya Date:-